Farm House is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by George Bessudo.
Stranded in the remote countryside after wrecking their car, a couple seeking to
start over discovers that there's no escape from the sins of their past.
Scarlet, played by Jamie Anne Allman.
Chad, played by William Lee Scott.
Samael, played by Steven Weber.
Rebecca, played by Drew Sidora.
Dr. Miller, played by Jack Donner.
Jonas, played by Sam Sarpong.
Farm House or The Farm House may refer to:
in the United States (by state)
Farm House (Urbana, Illinois), listed on the
National Register of Historic Places in Champaign County, Illinois
The Farm House (Knapp-Wilson House), a U.S.
National Historic Landmark on Iowa State University's campus
The Farm House (Bar Harbor, Maine), a summer estate
Farm
House (Bastrop, Texas), listed on the National Register of Historic Places in Bastrop County, Texas
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.